Title,Category,Type,Effect,FAQ text,image,site_capacity
Wrestlers,Order,Battle Plan,+ defense die if you sacrifice one warband in your force.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I sacrifice the last warband from a site, can the attacker still take it?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. They’ve already targeted it.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I have an Imperial Ally, can I sacrifice a warband from their board?', 'answer': 'A: If their board is adding warbands to your force, yes.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Wrestlers.webp,
Battle Honors,Order,Battle Plan,"If you're victorious, gain favor  favor from the suit\-order bank.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I take favor if the bank only has one left?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Battle%20Honors.webp,
Bear Traps,Order,Battle Plan,- dicer Kill one warband on the attacker's board.,"[{'question': 'Q: Does the killed warband remove a second attack die?', 'answer': 'A: Nope, you’ve already collected dice. You lose one warband and one attack die, exactly.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does the killed warband count forCursed Cauldron?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Bear%20Traps.webp,
Longbows,Order,Battle Plan,± dicer,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Longbows.webp,
Keep,Order,Battle Plan,+2 defense die if this site is targeted.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Keep.webp,
Pressgangs,Order,Muster,You can muster on cards that have favor or secret on them.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Pressgangs.webp,
Garrison,Order,,"When Played , gain one warband per site you rule, and put one warband from your board on each site you rule.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Garrison.webp,
Scouts,Order,Battle Plan,Gain 1 Supply.,"[{'question': 'Q: Does this Supply gain stack on top of powers that let me spend no Supply?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! You’ll end up gaining Supply by campaigning in this case, not losing it.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Scouts.webp,
Alchemist,Arcane,Power,Action : Gain favor  favor  favor  favor from any favor bank or banks.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Alchemist.webp,
Martial Culture,Order,Battle Plan,"If you're an Exile and defeat another Exile, you may become a Citizen- take no relic, end your Act Phase, and refresh supply to full .","[{'question': 'Q: Can I use this along withSecond Windand campaign a second time before becoming a Citizen?', 'answer': 'A: No. Second Wind says ‘after’, meaning you will resolve all your other battle plans first, including Martial Culture.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Martial%20Culture.webp,
Errand Boy,Beast,Power,You may draw from a discard pile in a different region instead of yours.,"[{'question': 'Q: Does this power stack withMushrooms?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. Guess he knows where all the good mushroom spots are.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I draw from the discard pile of another region, where do I discard to?', 'answer': 'A: Discard based on the region of your pawn. That Errand Boy is bringing everyone to you!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Errand%20Boy.webp,
Mercenaries,Discord,Power,"±3 dicer If you're defeated while using this power, discard Mercenaries.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Mercenaries.webp,
Tinker's Fair,Hearth,,"Action : Negotiate a binding exchange of favor , secret , and relics with any player.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Tinker's%20Fair.webp,
Rain Boots,Nomad,Battle Plan,"Ignore all your enemy's rolls of single shields shield . At end, discard Rain Boots.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Rain%20Boots.webp,
A Small Favor,Discord,,"When Played , Gain four warbands.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/A%20Small%20Favor.webp,
Second Wind,Discord,Power,"After you're victorious, you may travel and then may campaign, spending no Supply for either.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Second%20Wind.webp,
Sleight of Hand,Discord,Power,Action : Take secret from a player whose pawn is at your site. You cannot take their last secret .,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Sleight%20of%20Hand.webp,
Key to the City,Discord,,"When Played , if the ruler's pawn is not at this site, kill any warbands at this site, then gain a warband and place it here.","[{'question': 'Q: Can this be used against empty, bandit-ruled sites?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Key%20to%20the%20City.webp,
Scryer,Discord,Power,Action : Peek at any one discard pile.,"[{'question': 'Q: Do I get to look at the top card or the whole discard pile?', 'answer': 'A: The whole thing!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Scryer.webp,
Disgraced Captain,Discord,Power,+4 dicer if targeting a site that has an suit\-order card.,"[{'question': 'Q: Does this count if I target a pawn at a site with an Order card?', 'answer': 'A: No, you have to target the site itself. Of course, if you target a site and other things, this power takes effect.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Disgraced%20Captain.webp,
Naysayers,Discord,,"Rest : If any Exile is the Oathkeeper or Usurper, take favor from the Chancellor.","[{'question': 'Q: Does “any Exile” include myself?', 'answer': 'A: If you’re an Exile, yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Naysayers.webp,
Book Burning,Discord,Battle Plan,"Action : If you're victorious and targeted the defender's pawn, they also burn all of the secret on their board except their last.","[{'question': 'Q: If my enemy has any facedown secrets, do they have to burn them in any particular order?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. They burn all of their secrets except one, whether face up or down.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Book%20Burning.webp,
Ancient Binding,Nomad,Power,Action : Each player burns all their secret except their last.,"[{'question': 'Q: Do the secrets on the Darkest Secret get burned?', 'answer': 'A: Nope.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Ancient%20Binding.webp,
Horse Archers,Nomad,Battle Plan,"±3 dicer At end, discard Horse Archers.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Horse%20Archers.webp,
Warning Signals,Nomad,Battle Plan,"Move any warbands to and from your board and any sites you rule . At end, discard Warning Signals.","[{'question': 'Q: If I am a Citizen, do I need the Chancellor’s permission to move warbands (6.5)?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. This card is a way around that rule!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Warning%20Signals.webp,
Elders,Nomad,Power,Action : Gain favor .,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Elders.webp,
The Gathering,Nomad,,"When Played , any players in turn order may put their pawn on this site. Then, players with pawns here may negotiate binding exchanges of favor , secret , relics, and advisers.","[{'question': 'Q: How many exchanges can this prompt?', 'answer': 'A: As many as players want.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this go in turn order from the active player or from the Chancellor?', 'answer': 'A: From the Chancellor.'}, {'question': 'Q: Do pawns that go to the Gathering get returned to the sites that they came from?', 'answer': 'A: Nope!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/The%20Gathering.webp,
Faithful Friend,Nomad,,"When Played , gain 4 Supply.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Faithful%20Friend.webp,
Tents,Nomad,Power,Spend no Supply if you're traveling to a site in your region.,"[{'question': 'Q: How does this interact with theShrouded Wood?', 'answer': 'A: You must choose whether to use Tents at the start of the action. If the ruler makes you travel to another region, Tents does not work.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Tents.webp,
Great Herd,Nomad,,"When Played , you may swap Great Herd with a suit\-nomad card at any site.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I swap this with a locked card?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. A locked card cannot be discarded, moved or swapped.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Great%20Herd.webp,
Fire Talkers,Arcane,Power,±3 dicer if you hold the Darkest Secret.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I’m a Citizen and the Chancellor holds the Darkest Secret, do I get this bonus?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! Note that this is an errata, since the definition of ‘you’ (10) has changed.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Fire%20Talkers.webp,
Magician's Code,Arcane,Power,"If recovering the Darkest Secret, gain secret  secret and add them to any other secret you're paying to recover it .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Magician's%20Code.webp,
Spirit Snare,Arcane,Power,Action : Take favor from any one favor bank.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Spirit%20Snare.webp,
Wizard School,Arcane,Power,"Action : Gain secret , then end your Act Phase.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Wizard%20School.webp,
Dazzle,Arcane,,"When Played , discard all suit\-hearth and suit\-order cards at sites in your region.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Dazzle.webp,
Acting Troupe,Arcane,Trade,Act as if the Acting Troupe is a suit\-beast or suit\-order card instead.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I still use this as an Arcane card for trading?', 'answer': 'A: Yup! The Trade modifier is optional.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I treat this as other suits for stuff outside Trade?', 'answer': ""A: Nope! It's a Trade modifier, so it only works with the Trade action. This card is a bit less wacky than most.""}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Acting%20Troupe.webp,
Taming Charm,Arcane,Power,Action : Discard a suit\-beast or suit\-nomad card at your site to gain favor  favor from the matching favor bank.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I discard a card that has favor on it, does the favor return to its bank in time to take using this power?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Taming%20Charm.webp,
Inquisitor,Arcane,Power,"Action : Peek at an adviser of a player whose pawn is at your site. If it is the Conspiracy, you play it or discard it. If it is not, give them the favor here.","[{'question': 'Q: If I find the Conspiracy, can I play it facedown to my advisers?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Inquisitor.webp,
Wolves,Beast,Power,Action : Kill one warband on any one board.,"[{'question': 'Q: Why would I kill one of my own warbands?', 'answer': 'A: To refresh more Supply during your Rest Phase.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Wolves.webp,
Animal Playmates,Beast,Muster,Spend no Supply if you're mustering on a suit\-beast card.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Animal%20Playmates.webp,
True Names,Beast,Campaign,Your enemy cannot use battle plans that match any of your advisers against you.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/True%20Names.webp,
The Old Oak,Beast,Trade,"If trading with The Old Oak for secret , gain one more secret if you have any suit\-beast advisers.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/The%20Old%20Oak.webp,
Forest Paths,Beast,Power,Spend no Supply and ignore the powers of sites if you're traveling to a site with a suit\-beast card.,"[{'question': 'Q: Does this also let me ignore the powers of cards at the site I am traveling to, such asToll Roads?', 'answer': 'A: Nope, just the power of the site itself. It lets you get around things like theNarrow Pass.'}, {'question': 'Q: What happens if I use this when traveling from theShrouded Woodthat is ruled by an enemy?', 'answer': 'A: If the enemy ruler chooses that you travel to a Beast site, you pay no Supply. If you have less than 2 Supply, the enemy could either force your Travel action to fail, or could let you travel to a Beast site for free.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Forest%20Paths.webp,
Long-Lost Heir,Beast,,"When Played , if you're an Exile, you may become a Citizen- take no relic, end your Act Phase, and refresh Supply to full .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Long-Lost%20Heir.webp,
Rangers,Beast,Power,Ignore all skulls skull you roll. +2 dicer if the defense pool has 4+ defense die .,"[{'question': 'Q: If the defense pool has fewer than four dice when I use this power, but then the defender adds defense dice to their pool using their own battle plans, do I get +2 attack dice?', 'answer': 'A: No. You check this at the moment you use the power.'}, {'question': 'Q: Do I still ignore skulls even if I do not get the dice bonus?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Rangers.webp,
Roving Terror,Beast,Power,Action : Discard a denizen card at any other site and move this card there.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I move this card to a site with no denizens to discard?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! A slightly more accurate templating would be ‘Discard a denizen card at any site to move this card there.’'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Roving%20Terror.webp,
Wayside Inn,Hearth,Power,Action : Gain 2 Supply.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Wayside%20Inn.webp,
Extra Provisions,Hearth,Power,+2 defense die,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Extra%20Provisions.webp,
Memory of Home,Hearth,Power,Action : Move all favor from any one favor bank to the suit\-hearth bank.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Memory%20of%20Home.webp,
Welcoming Party,Hearth,Search,"If you play a denizen card that was not a facedown adviser, gain favor from the suit\-hearth bank.","[{'question': 'Q: Does this work if I play a card facedown in my advisers?', 'answer': 'A: No. More accurately, the card should say ‘If you play a denizen face up when first drawn, gain favor from the Hearth bank.’'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this power trigger when I play Welcoming Party itself?', 'answer': 'A: No.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Welcoming%20Party.webp,
Traveling Doctor,Hearth,Battle Plan,"If you're defeated, kill no warbands in your force and discard Traveling Doctor. Ignore powers that kill all of your force.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Traveling%20Doctor.webp,
Storyteller,Hearth,Power,Action : Place secret from the shared bank on the Darkest Secret.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I use this if the Darkest Secret is still in the shared bank?', 'answer': 'A: Yes, and any excess secrets will return to the shared bank when a player recovers it.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Storyteller.webp,
Armed Mob,Hearth,Power,Action : Discard a faceup adviser from a player who holds the Darkest Secret but not the People's Favor.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Armed%20Mob.webp,
Tavern Songs,Hearth,,Action : Peek at the top three cards of your region's discard pile.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Tavern%20Songs.webp,
Secret Signal,Arcane,Trade,"If you gain only one favor , gain one more favor .","[{'question': 'Q: If I am the Chancellor and have the Careless trait in the Imperial Reliquary, do I gain the extra favor if I trade for secrets?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Secret%20Signal.webp,
Augury,Arcane,Search,Action : Draw one more card.,"[{'question': 'Q: Does this let me draw two cards with Mushrooms?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. Guess you know where the good stuff is.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Augury.webp,
Rusting Ray,Arcane,Power,"If you hold the Darkest Secret, ignore all your enemy's rolls of hollow swords swordh .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Rusting%20Ray.webp,
Portal,Arcane,Power,Spend no Supply and ignore the powers of sites if you're traveling to or from this site.,"[{'question': 'Q: When can I use this power when traveling to its site?', 'answer': 'A: If you rule the site.'}, {'question': ""Q: Do I still have to pay for  Toll Roads if I'm using this power?"", 'answer': 'A: Yes. Sorry, a bit unthematic.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Portal.webp,
Billowing Fog,Arcane,Power,"If you're defeated, kill no warbands in your force. Ignore powers that kill all of your force.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Billowing%20Fog.webp,
Kindred Warriors,Arcane,Power,Ignore all skulls skull you roll. ±X dicer up to the number of other suits you rule.,"[{'question': ""Q: What does 'other suits' mean?"", 'answer': 'A: Suits other than the Arcane suit, which is the suit of Kindred Warriors.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Kindred%20Warriors.webp,
Terror Spells,Arcane,Power,Action : Kill any two warbands in your region if you hold the Darkest Secret.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I kill one at a site and one at another site, or one at a site and one on a board?', 'answer': 'A: Yes, you can mix and match however you want.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Terror%20Spells.webp,
Blood Pact,Arcane,Power,"Action : Sacrifice an even number of warbands on your board. For every two you sacrifice, gain secret .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Blood%20Pact.webp,
Revelation,Arcane,,"When Played , each player, following turn order, may burn any number of favor to gain an equal number of secret .","[{'question': 'Q: Do we start with the current player or the Chancellor?', 'answer': 'A: Start with the Chancellor and go in clockwise worder.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Revelation.webp,
Observatory,Arcane,Search,"While your pawn is here, you may draw from any one discard pile.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Observatory.webp,
Plague Engines,Arcane,Power,Action : Each player places one favor per site they rule into the suit\-arcane bank.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Plague%20Engines.webp,
Gleaming Armor,Arcane,Campaign,Your enemy's battle plans have an added cost of secret .,"[{'question': 'Q: If I am a Citizen and the Chancellor is attacked, does Gleaming Armor apply?', 'answer': 'A: Only if you join as an Ally.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I am an Exile, can I ever use this to help other Exiles who are being attacked?', 'answer': 'A: Nope!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Gleaming%20Armor.webp,
Bewitch,Arcane,,"When Played , if you're an Exile and have more secret  than the Chancellor, you may become a Citizen- take no relic, end your Act Phase, and refresh Supply to full.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Bewitch.webp,
Jinx,Arcane,Power,"If you rule Jinx, after you roll dicer or defense die for any reason, you may use this power to reroll all those dice once.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I use this card in any way to reroll the same set of dice multiple times?', 'answer': 'A: No. It is too subtle, but the word ‘once’ indicates that the dice cannot be rerolled multiple times.'}, {'question': 'Q: Do I pay for this card before or after rolling?', 'answer': 'A: After.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I use this to reroll dice forRelic ThieforGambling Hall?', 'answer': 'A: Yup! Jinx is templated super weirdly, as a persistent power rather than a battle plan, so you can do this.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Jinx.webp,
Tutor,Arcane,Power,Action : Gain secret,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Tutor.webp,
Dream Thief,Arcane,Power,Action : Swap any two facedown advisers.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Dream%20Thief.webp,
Cracking Ground,Arcane,Power,± dicer per site targeted.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Cracking%20Ground.webp,
Sealing Ward,Arcane,Campaign,Your relics add one more defense die when targeted.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Sealing%20Ward.webp,
Initiation Rite,Arcane,Muster,"To muster, you must place secret instead of favor .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Initiation%20Rite.webp,
Vow of Silence,Arcane,Recover,"You cannot recover the Darkest Secret or give anyone secret . Whenever a player recovers it, you gain X secret equal to the number of secret they placed.","[{'question': ""Q: How does this work if I haveWitch's Bargain?"", 'answer': 'A: Other players can still take your secrets, but you cannot use it to give away your secrets. Give and take are distinct keywords.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vow%20of%20Silence.webp,
Forgotten Vault,Arcane,Power,"Action : Place secret from the shared bank on the Darkest Secret, or burn secret from the Darkest Secret .","[{'question': 'Q: Can I use this to add a secret to the Darkest Secret if it is still in the shared bank?', 'answer': 'A: Yes, and any excess secrets will return to the shared bank when a player recovers it.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Forgotten%20Vault.webp,
Map Library,Arcane,Trade,"While your pawn is at this site, you may trade with a card at any site in your region.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Map%20Library.webp,
Witch's Bargain,Arcane,Power,"Action : Give secret to a player whose pawn is at your site to take favor  favor from them, or give favor  favor for secret , any number of times.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I take someone’s last secret? Most cards don’t allow this.', 'answer': 'A: Yup! You’re giving them favor, after all.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I affect multiple players at my site with one use of this card power?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}, {'question': 'Q: How does this work if I haveVow of Silence?', 'answer': 'A: You cannot use it to give away your secrets, but you can give favor to take secrets.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Witch's%20Bargain.webp,
Master of Disguise,Arcane,Power,Act as if you had another player's advisers instead.,"[{'question': 'Q: So can I use Trade modifiers in their advisers, likeMarriageandSecret Signal?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I use my other Trade modifiers before using Master of Disguise?', 'answer': 'A: No, you fully replace your advisers with another player’s advisers for the current Trade action.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I use this to get aroundVow of PovertyorVow of Kinship?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. Quite a sincere vow, right?'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Master%20of%20Disguise.webp,
Charlatan,Discord,,"When Played , burn all secret but one from the Darkest Secret.","[{'question': 'Q: Does this burn all secrets except for one on the Darkest Secret in play, or just from the Darkest Secret?', 'answer': 'A: From the Darkest Secret itself. Do not burn secrets that are not on the Darkest Secret.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Charlatan.webp,
Assassin,Discord,Power,You can only have two advisers. Action : Discard a faceup adviser of a player whose pawn is at your site.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I play this if I have two locked advisers already?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. You need to be able to fulfill your adviser capacity, and you would not be able to.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Assassin.webp,
Downtrodden,Discord,Muster,Gain two more warbands if mustering on a card whose favor bank has the least favor  .,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Downtrodden.webp,
Blackmail,Discord,,"When Played , choose a relic held by a player whose pawn is at your site. You take the relic unless they give you favor  favor  favor .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Blackmail.webp,
Cracked Sage,Discord,Power,±4 dicer if your enemy has an suit\-arcane adviser.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Cracked%20Sage.webp,
Dissent,Discord,,"When Played , each player, except the holder of the People's Favor, places one favor on this card for each suit of card they rule.","[{'question': 'Q: Does each Citizen have to place favor counting all the cards at Imperial sites?', 'answer': 'A: Yes they do. Citizens and the Chancellor all rule those sites.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Dissent.webp,
False Prophet,Discord,,"When Played , if you're an Exile, gain one warband and put it on any revealed Vision. You now also have it revealed. If it is ever discarded, kill the warband and play or discard the Vision as if you had searched.","[{'question': 'Q: Do I still have access to this Vision if I become a Citizen?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! The warband does not go away. However, you cannot win with it until you become an Exile again.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/False%20Prophet.webp,
Vow of Renewal,Discord,,"You cannot recover the People's Favor. Whenever any player burns favor , you take the favor instead.","[{'question': 'Q: Does taking burned favor include if someone recovers a relic from a site with a favor burn cost? What if I’m the one recovering it?', 'answer': 'A: Yup, you take the favor in all of those cases.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vow%20of%20Renewal.webp,
Zealots,Discord,Power,"If the defending force is larger than your force, each warband you sacrifice will add three to your attack.","[{'question': 'Q: If I use Zealots and later roll skulls in a way that makes my force smaller than the defending force, does Zealots trigger?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. Check whether your force is smaller than the defending force when you use the battle plan.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Zealots.webp,
Royal Ambitions,Discord,,"When Played , if you're an Exile and rule more sites than the Chancellor, you may become a Citizen- take any one Reliquary relic without peeking, end your Act Phase, and refresh Supply to full.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Royal%20Ambitions.webp,
Salt the Earth,Discord,,"You cannot play Salt the Earth to a site with any locked cards. When Played , ignore this site's capacity. Discard all other denizens at this site. This site's capacity is now 1.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I play this to theDrowned City?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}, {'question': 'Q: If this is at theDrowned City, can I replace it withFestival Districtin the Chronicle?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. Salt the Earth increases the capacity, so once it is gone, the site has no capacity for cards.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I play this to a facedown site?', 'answer': 'A: Nope!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Salt%20the%20Earth.webp,
Beast Tamer,Discord,Campaign,Enemies cannot use suit\-beast or suit\-nomad battle plans against you.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Beast%20Tamer.webp,
Riots,Discord,,"When Played , if the People's Favor is on the Mob side, discard all other cards of the most common suit on the map. If there is a tie, you choose among the tied suits.","[{'question': 'Q: What does ‘other’ mean on this card?', 'answer': 'A: If Discord happens to be the most common suit, do not discard Riots.'}, {'question': 'Q: Which cards count for the most common suit, and which get discarded exactly?', 'answer': 'A: Count and discard cards at all sites. Do not count or discard advisers.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Riots.webp,
Silver Tongue,Discord,,You can only have two advisers. Rest : Take favor from a favor bank matching a card at your site.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I play this if I have two locked advisers already?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. You need to be able to fulfill your adviser capacity, and you would not be able to.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Silver%20Tongue.webp,
Gambling Hall,Discord,Power,Action : Roll 4 defense die and take X favor equal to the total shield result from any one favor bank.,"[{'question': 'Q: Do rolls of 2x faces multiply the total result, like in a campaign?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Gambling%20Hall.webp,
Boiling Lake,Discord,Travel,"If you travel to this site and do not rule this card, you must kill two warbands on your board if able.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I be forced to travel here and lose warbands?', 'answer': 'A: Sure can.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Boiling%20Lake.webp,
Relic Thief,Discord,Power,"After a player takes any relics and their pawn is in your region, you may use this power to roll one defense die per relic taken. If you roll no shield / shield  shield , take the relics.","[{'question': 'Q: When exactly do I pay for this power?', 'answer': 'A: When you choose to use it, immediately after someone takes relics and they’re in your region.'}, {'question': 'Q: Could I use this on a player who just took a relic from me in a campaign?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! Pretty devious, right?'}, {'question': 'Q: Could I use this to take relics given in an exchange or from Citizenship offers?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. Very strictly, these are cases where a relic is given, rather than taken.'}, {'question': 'Q: When does the Oathkeeper title change hands if a relic is taken and then taken again with Relic Thief?', 'answer': 'A: Check for who holds the most relics at each moment that relics change hands, not after the entire process of multiple players taking relics.'}, {'question': 'Q: Do I evaluate the results of the roll all at once, or one die at a time?', 'answer': 'A: All at once. It is less likely that you succeed on the roll with more relics, but you will get all of them if you do succeed.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Relic%20Thief.webp,
Enchantress,Discord,Power,Action : Swap this card with any faceup adviser.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I swap this for thePied Piperand they already have four cards, what happens?', 'answer': 'A: They will need to discard a card from their advisers, but not the Enchantress.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Enchantress.webp,
Insomnia,Discord,,You can only have two advisers. Rest : Gain secret .,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I play this if I have two locked advisers already?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. You need to be able to fulfill your adviser capacity, and you would not be able to.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Insomnia.webp,
Sneak Attack,Discord,Campaign,"After another player's campaign, you may campaign, spending no Supply, if you declare them as the defender.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I attack someone who does not rule my site and whose pawn is not at my site?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. You must follow the normal Campaign rules for declaring a defender.'}, {'question': 'Q: When exactly do I campaign?', 'answer': 'A: Immediately after the triggering player ends their campaign.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I use this power if the attacker usedSecond Wind?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. Resolve Sneak Attack first, then Second Wind.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Sneak%20Attack.webp,
Gossip,Discord,,Enemies of Gossip's ruler cannot play cards as facedown advisers.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I only draw one card but cannot play it face up, what do I do?', 'answer': 'A: Discard it, following the normal rules.'}, {'question': 'Q: If the bandits rule this, who does it affect?', 'answer': 'A: Every player!'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this force enemies to flip up their current facedown advisers?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. Any advisers that are currently facedown can remain facedown.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this affect the facing of advisers during setup?', 'answer': 'A: Nope.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Gossip.webp,
Bandit Chief,Discord,,"When Played , kill one warband at each site. While Bandit Chief is faceup, each site has two more bandits.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Bandit%20Chief.webp,
Chaos Cult,Discord,,"After another player takes the Oathkeeper title, you take favor from them.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Chaos%20Cult.webp,
Slander,Discord,Power,"If you're victorious and targeted the defender's pawn, they burn all of the favor on their board .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Slander.webp,
Code of Honor,Order,Battle Plan,±2 dicer but you cannot use other battle plans.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I’m the Chancellor and I’m joining a campaign as an Imperial Ally to a Citizen defender, does using this battle plan mean that the Citizen defender can’t use other battle plans?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. This is an errata from the rules as written.'}, {'question': 'Q: If the bandits rule Code of Honor as well as other battle plans that they can use, which battle plans will they use when defending in a campaign?', 'answer': 'A: They will use Code of Honor and no others.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Code%20of%20Honor.webp,
Outriders,Order,Battle Plan,Ignore all skulls skull you roll.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Outriders.webp,
Messenger,Order,Power,Action : Move any warbands to and from your board and any sites you rule .,"[{'question': 'Q: If I am a Citizen, do I have to ask the Chancellor for permission ($rule: 6.5$)', 'answer': 'A: Nope. This is a way to get around it.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Messenger.webp,
Field Promotion,Order,Power,"If you're victorious, gain three warbands.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Field%20Promotion.webp,
Palanquin,Order,Power,"Action : Choose a player whose pawn is at your site. Put your pawn on a site that they can travel to. Make them travel to that site, spending no Supply.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I use Palanquin to go to a site withToll Roads?', 'answer': 'A: Yes, but the player whose pawn is at your site must choose to give a favor to Toll Roads’ ruler, if they don’t rule it themself.'}, {'question': 'Q: If we’re both at theShrouded Wood, who chooses where we go?', 'answer': 'A: You will always go to the site that you choose, as long as the other player could travel there. If you rule the Shrouded Wood, you choose their destination, which can be different from the site that you go to. If they rule the Shrouded Wood, they will travel to the same site as you. If a third party rules the Shrouded Wood, the third party will choose where the player travels.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Palanquin.webp,
Shield Wall,Order,Power,"+2 defense die If you're defeated, kill all of your force.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Shield%20Wall.webp,
Military Parade,Order,Battle Plan,"If you're victorious, gain favor from the favor banks matching each adviser of your enemy .","[{'question': 'Q: What happens if my enemy has multiple advisers of the same suit?', 'answer': 'A: Take one favor per adviser of that suit. So if they have two Hearth advisers, take two favor from the Hearth bank.'}, {'question': 'Q: What happens if the bandits rule this and are victorious?', 'answer': 'A: Burn the gained favor. I will likely add a clarifying rule to always burn favor going to bandits, since this behavior is baked into cards likeToll Roads.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Military%20Parade.webp,
Tome Guardians,Order,,Enemies of Tome Guardians' ruler cannot target or take the Darkest Secret in any way.,"[{'question': 'Q: If the bandits rule this card, can anyone recover the Darkest Secret?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! For completeness, the definition of ‘enemy’ in the Glossary should also say that the bandits consider all players enemies.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Tome%20Guardians.webp,
Tyrant,Order,Travel,"You must kill a warband at the site you travel to, if able.","[{'question': 'Q: If there are no warbands at the site I travel to, do I have to kill a warband on my board?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. It’s one at the site.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I still travel to a site if there are no warbands there?', 'answer': 'A: Yup. That’s what the “if able” signifies (10).'}, {'question': 'Q: If I travel to a site that has only one of my warbands on it, do I have to kill it? Pretty please no?', 'answer': 'A: Sorry, you have to kill it!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Tyrant.webp,
Forced Labor,Order,Search,Enemies cannot search if their pawn is at any site ruled by Forced Labor's ruler unless they give favor to its ruler.,"[{'question': 'Q: Does this card power apply if I am playing a facedown card (6.1)?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! As it says in the rules, modifiers do apply.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I paid for Forced Labor once when playing facedown, would I have to pay again to play it face up?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! Servitude is not pleasant.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Forced%20Labor.webp,
Secret Police,Order,,Enemies cannot play Visions faceup while their pawn is at any site ruled by Secret Police's ruler.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Secret%20Police.webp,
Specialist,Order,Power,The defender cannot use battle plans.,"[{'question': 'Q: So if I am attacking the Empire and use this, can Imperial Allies use battle plans?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. In these situations, consider ‘defender’ to mean the entire defending side.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Specialist.webp,
Captains,Order,Power,Action : Campaign at any site you rule. Act as if your pawn is there. Spend no Supply and add your warbands there to your force.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I am a Citizen, can I use this to campaign against the Chancellor or another Citizen?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! Even though you lose access to the card one you start the campaign, you were still able to use it to start the campaign.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I am a Citizen and attack another Citizen or the Chancellor, do I still add the warbands at the site to my force?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. They do not get added to the defending force, and you do not need to target the site.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Captains.webp,
Siege Engines,Order,Power,Action : Kill two warbands at any one site in your region.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Siege%20Engines.webp,
Royal Tax,Order,,When Played : take favor  favor from each player whose pawn is at a site you rule in your pawn's region.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Royal%20Tax.webp,
Toll Roads,Order,Travel,Enemies cannot travel to sites ruled by Toll Roads' ruler unless they give favor to its ruler.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I be forced to travel here?', 'answer': 'A: Only if you choose to pay the favor toll or if you do not need to.'}, {'question': 'Q: Do I have to pay the bandits when traveling to a facedown site?', 'answer': 'A: No, since no one rules facedown sites.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Toll%20Roads.webp,
Curfew,Order,Trade,Enemies cannot trade with cards ruled by Curfew's ruler unless they give favor to its ruler.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Curfew.webp,
Knights Errant,Order,Muster,"After mustering, you may campaign, spending no Supply.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Knights%20Errant.webp,
Vow of Obedience,Order,,You cannot play Visions faceup. Rest : Take favor from any one favor bank.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I already have a face-up Vision, do I have to discard it?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! You just cannot play any new ones.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I play the Conspiracy if I have this?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! The Conspiracy is a Vision.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vow%20of%20Obedience.webp,
Hunting Party,Order,Search,"After searching the world deck, you may campaign, spending no Supply.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Hunting%20Party.webp,
Council Seat,Order,,"If you're a Citizen, you cannot be exiled, even by yourself.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Council%20Seat.webp,
Encirclement,Order,Power,±2 dicer if your force is larger than your enemy's.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Encirclement.webp,
Peace Envoy,Order,Power,"You cannot use other battle plans. If your enemy's pawn is at your site, give them one favor per defense die in the pool. You're victorious now. Ignore killing warbands.","[{'question': 'Q: If I am attacking a player who has Imperial Allies, do I have to give the favor to all of them?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. Give the favor to the player you are attacking.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I don’t have the favor to give, can I still be victorious?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. Consider the favor you’re giving them as part of the cost to use the power.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I use this when targeting their pawn and favor, thus burning some of the favor I give them?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. Also you are a terrible person and I love it.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Peace%20Envoy.webp,
Relic Hunter,Order,Battle Plan,"You may target facedown relics at targeted sites, adding 1 defense die per relic. You may put any relics you take on the bottom of the relic deck.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I target a relic at a site I already rule?', 'answer': 'A: No, you must be targeting the site as well.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Relic%20Hunter.webp,
Homesteaders,Hearth,,Action : Move one of your faceup advisers to your site.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Homesteaders.webp,
Crop Rotation,Hearth,Search,"If playing to a site, you may discard a denizen there first.","[{'question': ""Q: Can I use this along with the $link:Banner of the People's Favor?$"", 'answer': 'A: Yup!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Crop%20Rotation.webp,
A Round of Ale,Hearth,Power,"Action : Return all favor and secret , and flip your secret , as in the Rest Phase, except for the favor here.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/A%20Round%20of%20Ale.webp,
Land Warden,Hearth,Power,You may play two cards you draw if you play at least one card to a site.,"[{'question': ""Q: If I use this to play two cards to site, can I use theBanner of the People's Favortwice?"", 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I play a card facedown as long as I play the other to a site?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Land%20Warden.webp,
Charming Friend,Hearth,Power,Action : Take favor from a player whose pawn is at your site.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Charming%20Friend.webp,
Village Constable,Hearth,Battle Plan,±2 dicer unless your enemy has the People's Favor.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Village%20Constable.webp,
Family Heirloom,Hearth,,"When Played , draw a relic. Take it or put it on the bottom of the relic deck.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Family%20Heirloom.webp,
News from Afar,Hearth,Power,Spend no Supply.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/News%20from%20Afar.webp,
Levelers,Hearth,Power,Action : Move favor  favor from the favor bank from the most favor to that with the least favor . You decide ties.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Levelers.webp,
Fabled Feast,Hearth,,"When Played , take X favor equal to the number of suit\-hearth cards you rule from any one favor bank.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Fabled%20Feast.webp,
The Great Levy,Hearth,Power,"±3 dicer and ignore all skulls skull you roll, unless your enemy has the People's Favor.","[{'question': ""Q: Does the “unless your enemy has the People's Favor” restriction apply to both the skull cancellation and attack dice?"", 'answer': ""A: Yes, the entire power is canceled if your enemy has the People's Favor.""}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/The%20Great%20Levy.webp,
Hearts and Minds,Hearth,Power,"As defender, you're victorious now. At end, discard Hearts and Minds unless you hold the People's Favor.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Hearts%20and%20Minds.webp,
Relic Breaker,Hearth,Power,Action : Put a facedown relic at your site on the bottom of the relic deck to gain three warbands.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Relic%20Breaker.webp,
Book Binders,Hearth,Search,"After another player plays a Vision faceup, you gain favor  favor from any one favor bank.","[{'question': 'Q: Does this include theConspiracy?', 'answer': 'A: Yup!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Book%20Binders.webp,
Ballot Box,Hearth,,"Action : If you're an Exile and have the People's Favor, become a Citizen- take no relic, end your Act Phase, and refresh Supply to full.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Ballot%20Box.webp,
Saddle Makers,Hearth,Search,"After another player plays a suit\-nomad or suit\-order card, you gain favor  favor from the matching favor bank.","[{'question': 'Q: When exactly do I gain the favor?', 'answer': 'A: Immediately after resolving the text in the relevant5.1.4subsection. So they gain favor for playing to site first, for example, but resolve When Played powers (7.3.3) after Saddle Makers.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Saddle%20Makers.webp,
Herald,Hearth,Campaign,"After another player campaigns against a player , you gain favor from any favor bank.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Herald.webp,
Rowdy Pub,Hearth,Muster,Gain one more warband if mustering from Rowdy Pub.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Rowdy%20Pub.webp,
Vow of Peace,Hearth,Campaign,You cannot campaign. Attackers cannot sacrifice warbands to increase their attack against you.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I’m the Chancellor, can Citizens campaign?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! They are only Allies during an ongoing defensive campaign.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vow%20of%20Peace.webp,
Deed Writer,Hearth,,"Action : Negotiate a binding exchange of favor , secret , and ruled sites with any player. Old ruler moves warbands to board, and new ruler moves warbands from board.","[{'question': 'Q: Wait, can I make a deal with an Exile if I’m a Citizen?', 'answer': 'A: Sure can. No permission needed from the Chancellor, and you take the warbands.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I buy sites as a Citizen, can I make the Chancellor place warbands?', 'answer': 'A: No. Interpret uses of ‘board’ as meaning ‘your board.’'}, {'question': 'Q: Can a Citizen and Chancellor exchange sites to move around warbands?', 'answer': 'A: No. You cannot give away these sites to each other since you both rule them already.'}, {'question': 'Q: Exactly how many warbands does the new rules have to place?', 'answer': 'A: Any number they want, but not zero unless they have theBandit Crown.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can a site be exchanged if the person receiving it has no warbands to rule it?', 'answer': 'A: No, unless they would rule it by having theBandit Crown.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Deed%20Writer.webp,
Salad Days,Hearth,,"When Played , gain favor  favor  favor - one each from three different favor banks.","[{'question': 'Q: If I play this to a site, do I still get the normal favor for playing to site?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Salad%20Days.webp,
Marriage,Hearth,,"Marriage counts as two suit\-hearth advisers, but only counts as one toward your adviser limit.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Marriage.webp,
Hospital,Hearth,Battle Plan,"If any of your warbands would be killed, place them on Hospital's site instead if you still rule it.","[{'question': 'Q: When exactly do I place the warbands saved from being killed?', 'answer': ""A: At the end of the campaign. More accurately, the card should read ‘If any of your warbands would be killed, place them on Hospital's site instead if you rule it at the end.’""}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Hospital.webp,
Awaited Return,Hearth,Trade,Spend no Supply if you sacrifice one warband from your board.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Awaited%20Return.webp,
Convoys,Nomad,Power,Action : Take another region's discard pile and put it on top of your region's discard pile .,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Convoys.webp,
Vow of Kinship,Nomad,,Move all of your favor to the suit\-nomad bank. Any favor you gain or take is put in the suit\-nomad bank. You can use favor in the suit\-nomad bank as if it is on your board.,"[{'question': 'Q: Do cards like $Royal Tax$ take favor from the Nomad bank now?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. You can use favor in the Nomad bank, but it is not favor on your board.'}, {'question': ""Q: If I have theBanner of the People's Favorwith only one favor, does its Wake power force me to take from the Nomad bank?"", 'answer': 'A: No. You can use Nomad favor as if it is on your board, but you are not forced to.'}, {'question': ""Q: If someone gives me favor, such as by usingWitch's Bargain, does it go on my board or in the Nomad bank?"", 'answer': 'A: It goes to the Nomad bank. More accurately, the card should say ‘any favor going to your board’ instead of ‘any favor you gain or take.’'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vow%20of%20Kinship.webp,
Wild Mounts,Nomad,Battle Plan,"If you would discard any number of suit\-nomad battle plans, you may instead discard any one suit\-beast you rule.","[{'question': 'Q: Can the bandits use this?', 'answer': 'A: If they would discard two or more Nomads, they discard the first Beast card they rule starting at the top of the Cradle and going down through the regions.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Wild%20Mounts.webp,
Lancers,Nomad,Battle Plan,"Double your total attack roll. At end, discard Lancers.","[{'question': 'Q: Does my attack roll include skulls?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. Basically, act as if you got all your dice results twice.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Lancers.webp,
Mountain Giant,Nomad,Power,"±1 dicer or ±3. At end, discard.","[{'question': 'Q: Is the card discarded if I choose +/-1 attack die?', 'answer': 'A: No, only if you choose +/- 3.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Mountain%20Giant.webp,
Rival Khan,Nomad,Battle Plan,"±4 dicer if your enemy has a suit\-nomad adviser. At end, discard Rival Khan.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Rival%20Khan.webp,
Lost Tongue,Nomad,,Other players cannot target or take your relics or banners in any way unless they rule a suit\-nomad card.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Lost%20Tongue.webp,
Special Envoy,Nomad,Travel,"Spend no Supply. After traveling, end your Act Phase.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Special%20Envoy.webp,
Resettle,Nomad,,Action : Move a faceup suit\-nomad card from any player's advisers to any site.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Resettle.webp,
Oracle,Nomad,Power,Action : Draw the Vision closest to the top of the world deck. Play or discard it as if you searched.,"[{'question': 'Q: Does this increase the Visions Drawn track?', 'answer': 'A: Yes.'}, {'question': 'Q: Where do I put the other cards from the World Deck that I handled?', 'answer': 'A: Put them back on the World Deck in the same order.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I discard the Vision, can I useCracked Hornto put it at the bottom of the world deck?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I play the Vision in my advisers facedown?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I play this card if I am at a site with  Forced Labor and have no favor to pay?', 'answer': 'A: No. This saddens me, but the wording on the card is just like the minor action to flip facedown advisers, so it has to be this way.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Oracle.webp,
Pilgrimage,Nomad,,"When Played , move all denizens at your site to the Dispossessed. Shuffle and draw denizens from the Dispossessed equal to the number you moved. Peek at them and put them on your region's discard pile.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Pilgrimage.webp,
Spell Breaker,Nomad,,Enemies of Spell Breaker's ruler cannot use powers that cost any secret or secretb .,"[{'question': 'Q: Does the cost include any secret cost added byGleaming Armor?', 'answer': 'A: Yes.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this include theBuried GiantandThe Hidden Placesite powers?', 'answer': 'A: Yes.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this prevent the Conspiracy from being played against me?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! The Conspiracy power has a cost of a secret burn.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this prevent mustering from Initiation Rite?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! Mustering is not a power.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Spell%20Breaker.webp,
Mounted Patrol,Nomad,Battle Plan,"The attacker rolls only half the dicer in their attack pool, rounded down. At end, discard Mounted Patrol.","[{'question': 'Q: Does this halve the attack dice after using other battle plans or before?', 'answer': 'A: It modifies how many dice ‘the attacker rolls’, so it halves the final number modified by battle plans.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Mounted%20Patrol.webp,
Great Crusade,Nomad,Battle Plan,"± dicer per suit\-nomad card you rule. At end, discard Great Crusade.","[{'question': 'Q: Does this include itself in the number of nomad cards ruled?', 'answer': 'A: Yes.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Great%20Crusade.webp,
Ancient Bloodline,Nomad,,Your enemies act as if denizens and relics at sites you rule are locked .,"[{'question': 'Q: What are the implications of relics being locked?', 'answer': 'A: They can’t be recovered or discarded or otherwise messed with. They’re stuck at the site, except for Ancient Bloodline’s ruler.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this only apply in campaigns?', 'answer': 'A: No, it always applies. More accurately, the text should read ‘Enemies’ rather than ‘Your enemies’ to avoid confusion with battle plans that use this terminology.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Ancient%20Bloodline.webp,
Ancient Pact,Nomad,,"When Played , you may give the Chancellor the Darkest Secret to become a Citizen- take any one Reliquary relic without peeking, end your Act Phase, and refresh Supply to full.","[{'question': 'Q: If I am a Citizen, can I give the Darkest Secret to the Chancellor to simply take a relic from the Reliquary?', 'answer': 'A: No. For consistency, this card should say ‘if you are an Exile’.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Ancient%20Pact.webp,
Storm Caller,Nomad,Battle Plan,"+2 defense die At end, discard Storm Caller.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Storm%20Caller.webp,
Family Wagon,Nomad,,You can only have one adviser that is not a suit\-nomad . You can have any number of suit\-nomad advisers- they ignore your adviser limit.,"[{'question': 'Q: How does this interact withPied Piper?', 'answer': 'A: You can always play Pied Piper after Family Wagon. If you play Family Wagon after Pied Piper, you can only keep one non-Nomad adviser, so you could keep Pied Piper or one other non-Nomad card. (This ruling has changed.)'}, {'question': 'Q: What happens if I play this into my advisers and already have three Nomad advisers?', 'answer': 'A: Nothing, this is okay. You check whether to discard based on the new adviser limit prompted by the card you are playing. In this case, Family Wagon will increase your adviser limit and allow you to play without discarding. (This ruling has changed.)'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Family%20Wagon.webp,
Way Station,Nomad,Travel,Spend no Supply if you're traveling to this site and either rule Way Station or choose to give favor to its ruler.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Way%20Station.webp,
Twin Brother,Nomad,,"When Played , you may swap this card with a faceup suit\-nomad adviser of another player.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Twin%20Brother.webp,
Hospitality,Nomad,Travel,"After traveling, gain favor from one favor bank that matches both a card at your site and one of your advisers.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Hospitality.webp,
A Fast Steed,Nomad,Power,Spend no Supply if you have three or fewer warbands on your board.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/A%20Fast%20Steed.webp,
Relic Worship,Nomad,Recover,"After you recover a relic, gain 3 Supply.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Relic%20Worship.webp,
Sacred Ground,Nomad,Search,"Players cannot play Visions, except the Conspiracy, faceup, unless their pawn is at this site.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Sacred%20Ground.webp,
Nature Worship,Beast,Power,± dicer per suit\-beast adviser you have.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Nature%20Worship.webp,
Birdsong,Beast,Trade,Spend no Supply if you're trading with a suit\-beast or suit\-nomad card.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Birdsong.webp,
Small Friends,Beast,Trade,Act as if your pawn is at any site with a suit\-beast card.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I use Trade modifiers at the site my pawn is physically at, in addition to the site I am acting as if I am at?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! Only the new site.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Small%20Friends.webp,
Grasping Vines,Beast,Travel,Enemies traveling from any site ruled by Grasping Vines' ruler must kill one warband on their board if able.,"[{'question': 'Q: What if I don’t have any warbands?', 'answer': 'A: Not a problem. You only kill one if you have any on your board.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I be forced to travel from a site affected by this card, and make me lose warbands?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Grasping%20Vines.webp,
Threatening Roar,Beast,,"When Played , discard all suit\-nomad and suit\-beast cards at sites in your region.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Threatening%20Roar.webp,
Fae Merchant,Beast,Power,Action : Draw a relic and take it. Put any relic you hold except the Grand Scepter on the bottom of the relic deck.,"[{'question': 'Q: In the Oathkeeper of Protection, if I get the most relics before I return a relic to the deck, do I take the Oathkeeper title?', 'answer': 'A: No. Only count your number of relics after you have completed this action.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Fae%20Merchant.webp,
Second Chance,Beast,Power,Action : Kill one warband on the board of a player who has an suit\-order or suit\-discord adviser to gain one warband.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Second%20Chance.webp,
Pied Piper,Beast,Power,This card ignores the adviser limit. Action : Move this card to any other player's advisers. Take favor  favor from them.,"[{'question': 'Q: Does the secret I pay to use this card move with the card?', 'answer': 'A: Yes, but you will still get it back in your Rest Phase.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I play this card if I already have three advisers?', 'answer': 'A: Yes, because it ignores the adviser limit. But note that it does not reduce the total number of advisers you have!'}, {'question': 'Q: If I have three advisers, including this card, can I play and keep a fourth adviser?', 'answer': 'A: No. Pied Piper itself ignores the adviser limit, so it does not prompt a discard when you play it, but it still counts toward your total number of advisers.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Pied%20Piper.webp,
Mushrooms,Beast,Power,"Spend no Supply, but draw only one card from the bottom of your region's discard pile.","[{'question': 'Q: Does this card stack with powers likeAuguryand theGreedytrait?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Mushrooms.webp,
Insect Swarm,Beast,Campaign,Your enemy's battle plans each have an added cost of favorb .,"[{'question': 'Q: Does this affect the battle plans of players who are not involved in the campaign?', 'answer': ""A: No. The term 'your enemy' refers to those involved in the campaign. Admittedly, this is somewhat confusing. Sorry!""}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Insect%20Swarm.webp,
Vow of Union,Beast,,"In campaigns, warbands at sites you rule add to your attacking force. You cannot travel from a site you rule if any warbands are on your board.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I use this to remove or sacrifice the last warband of mine off a site?', 'answer': 'A: Yes you can. This gets around the restriction in the relevant minor action (6.5).'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I not add warbands at my sites to my attacking force?', 'answer': 'A: Nope, as with the other vows, you gotta do it.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this allow me to redistribute warbands from my attacking force across the sites I rule?', 'answer': 'A: No. You can choose where to remove them from, but you cannot freely redistribute.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can someone make me travel if I have this?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! For example, banishing your pawn would only burn half your favor.'}, {'question': 'Q: How does this work if I haveBandit Crown?', 'answer': 'A: Add the bandit warbands to your attacking force. You could not kill or sacrifice the bandit warbands, only your physical warbands. Expect your Bandit Crown to get stolen soon!'}, {'question': 'Q: If I am a Citizen attacking a Citizen or the Chancellor, do I add purple warbands at sites to my attacking force?', 'answer': 'A: No. During this campaign you are not an Imperial player, so you do not rule sites that have purple warbands on them.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vow%20of%20Union.webp,
Giant Python,Beast,Campaign,"Whenever a player attacks you, they must declare targets that add an even total of defense die to your defense pool.","[{'question': 'Q: Does this count things like the Oathkeeper bonus and defense dice added by battle plans?', 'answer': 'A: Nope, Giant Python specifies that it only counts defense dice added by declaring targets, which the Oathkeeper bonus and battle plans are not.'}, {'question': 'Q: How does this interact with Sprawling Ramparts?', 'answer': 'A: Sites now add two dice each, so it would be legal to target one site alone. However, you could not target one site and a relic that added one defense die, as this would be a total of three added defense dice.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I am an Imperial player and an Imperial Ally has this, does this take effect?', 'answer': 'A: If the Chancellor has it, it takes effect, since they are always an Ally. If a Citizen has it, it does not take effect, since targets were already declared.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Giant%20Python.webp,
War Tortoise,Beast,Power,Ignore all attack or defense added by your enemy's rolls of sword  sword  skull or shield  shield .,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/War%20Tortoise.webp,
New Growth,Beast,Search,You may play suit\-beast and suit\-hearth cards to any site .,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/New%20Growth.webp,
Wild Cry,Beast,Search,"If you play a suit\-beast card, gain 1 Supply and 2 warbands.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Wild%20Cry.webp,
Animal Host,Beast,,"When Played , gain warbands equal to the total number of suit\-beast cards at any sites .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Animal%20Host.webp,
Memory of Nature,Beast,Power,Action : Move a total of X favor from any favor banks to the suit\-beast bank. X is the number of suit\-beast cards on the map.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Memory%20of%20Nature.webp,
Marsh Spirit,Beast,Campaign,Players who target this site cannot use battle plans.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Marsh%20Spirit.webp,
Vow of Poverty,Beast,,"You cannot gain favor from Trade. Rest : If you have no favor , take favor  favor from any one favor bank.","[{'question': 'Q: How does this interact with the Careless trait?', 'answer': 'A: You still don’t get the favor from Careless.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vow%20of%20Poverty.webp,
Forest Council,Beast,,Enemies of Forest Council's rule cannot trade with or must from suit\-beast cards.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Forest%20Council.webp,
Walled Garden,Beast,Battle Plan,± defense die per suit\-beast at any sites if this site is targeted.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Walled%20Garden.webp,
Vow of Beastkin,Beast,Muster,"You must muster on a card that matching any of your advisers, but you gain one more warband.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vow%20of%20Beastkin.webp,
Bracken,Beast,Search,You may put all the cards you discard on the top or bottom of any one discard pile .,"[{'question': ""Q: Does this include cards discarded from theBanner of the People's Favoror cards likeDazzle?"", 'answer': ""A: It includes any cards discarded during the Search action, so it includes the People's Favor, but not cards likeDazzle.""}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Bracken.webp,
Wild Allies,Beast,Power,Action : Campaign at any site with a suit\-beast card. Act as if your pawn is there. Spend no Supply and add your warbands there to your force.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Wild%20Allies.webp,
Sprawling Rampart,Edifice,Order,Each site ruled by Sprawling Rampart's ruler adds one more defense die when targeted.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Sprawling%20Rampart.webp,
Bandit Rampart,Edifice,Order,-2 dicer if this site is targeted.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Bandit%20Rampart.webp,
Hall of Debate,Edifice,Hearth,Players cannot target the People's Favor,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Hall%20of%20Debate.webp,
Hall of Mockery,Edifice,Hearth,Recovering the People's Favor always flips it to the Mob side.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Hall%20of%20Mockery.webp,
Forest Temple,Edifice,Beast,"In the Chronicle, do not discard sites with any suit\-beast cards.","[{'question': 'Q: Does this protect sites from being discarded even if the winner does not rule it?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! It will become a ruin later in the Chronicle, though.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does this protect sites immediately after being built, or only in the next Chronicle?', 'answer': 'A: It immediately protects sites.'}, {'question': 'Q: If a site has a Beast card and an edifice, but the winner does not rule it, does Forest Temple protect it from getting ruined?', 'answer': 'A: No. All Forest Temple does is prevent a site discard, not whether an edifice degrades to a ruin from lack of rule.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Forest%20Temple.webp,
Ruined Temple,Edifice,Beast,Enemies of Ruined Temple's ruler cannot play suit\-beast cards faceup.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Ruined%20Temple.webp,
Festival District,Edifice,Discord,"Action : Negotiate a binding exchange of favor , secret , and advisers with any player.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Festival%20District.webp,
Squalid District,Edifice,Discord,"Whenever the dicer is rolled to end the game, Squalid District's ruler may increase or decrease this roll by one. Citizens cannot use this power.","[{'question': 'Q: Do I modify the die roll before or after rolling?', 'answer': 'A: After, although it is doubtful this will ever matter.'}, {'question': 'Q: What happens if I roll a 6 and increase the number?', 'answer': 'A: The game still ends.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Squalid%20District.webp,
Great Spire,Edifice,Arcane,You may swap any number of denizens you draw with random cards from the Dispossessed.,"[{'question': 'Q: If I have theTruthful Harp, what do I have to reveal?', 'answer': 'A: The cards you draw from the deck or discard pile, and the specific card you keep, but not swapped Dispossessed cards that you do not keep.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Great%20Spire.webp,
Fallen Spire,Edifice,Arcane,Action : Swap up to five denizens from the top of your region's discard pile with random cards from the Dispossessed.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I look at the top five cards before I choose how many to swap?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. You choose how many you want to swap without peeking at all. You better know what is in there if you want to get rid of specific cards!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Fallen%20Spire.webp,
Ancient Forge,Edifice,Nomad,Action : Draw a relic. Take it or put it on the bottom of the relic deck.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Ancient%20Forge.webp,
Broken Forge,Edifice,Nomad,Action : Flip this card over.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Broken%20Forge.webp,
Sticky Fire,Relic,Battle Plan,"If you're victorious, you may kill all the warbands in your enemy's force. If you do, you must give them favor if able.","[{'question': 'Q: If I am attacking a player who has Imperial Allies, do I have to give a favor to each of them?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. Give the favor to the player that you are attacking.'}, {'question': 'Q: If my enemy uses a card likeTraveling Doctorto ignore this, do I still give the favor?', 'answer': 'A: Yes. More accurately, the card should say ‘If you choose to’ rather than ‘If you do.’'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Sticky%20Fire.webp,
Cursed Cauldron,Relic,Battle Plan,"If you're victorious, gain one warband per enemy warband killed in this campaign.","[{'question': 'Q: How does this interact withHospital?', 'answer': 'A: Hospital prevents warbands from being killed, so you don’t gain warbands for them.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I am a Citizen and campaign against the Chancellor or another Citizen, what color of warbands do I gain?', 'answer': 'A: You still gain purple warbands.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Cursed%20Cauldron.webp,
Brass Horse,Relic,Power,"Action : Reveal the top card of your discard pile. Travel to a site with a card of this suit. If unable, travel as normal. In either case, spend no Supply.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I use this if my region’s discard pile is empty?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! You have to reveal a card.'}, {'question': 'Q: What happens if I reveal a Vision card from the top of the discard pile?', 'answer': 'A: It does not match anything, so you can travel anywhere. Congratulations!'}, {'question': 'Q: Where does the card go after I reveal it?', 'answer': 'A: Just put it back on the discard pile facedown.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I use this to travel from theShrouded Wood, but an enemy rules it, what happens?', 'answer': 'A: The ruler chooses your destination site from among the possible ones allowed by Brass Horse.'}, {'question': 'Q: What happens if the only site with a matching suit is the site where my pawn is?', 'answer': 'A: You can travel to any other site, since when you Travel you move to a different site.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Brass%20Horse.webp,
Truthful Harp,Relic,Search,"You may choose to draw two more cards. If you do, you must reveal every card you draw and the card you keep.","[{'question': 'Q: Does this let me avoid stopping when I draw a Vision from the world deck?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. You still stop if you draw one.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I choose to draw two more cards after I draw the original amount?', 'answer': ""A: No. As with other action modifiers, you choose whether to use it at the start of the action it modifies. A clearer wording might be 'Draw two more cards. If you use this power, you must reveal every card you draw and the card you keep.'""}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Truthful%20Harp.webp,
Grand Mask,Relic,,"If you're an Exile, during your turn you rule cards except battle plans at Imperial sites, and Imperial players do not.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I use this to get around the power of theShrouded Woodif the Chancellor rules it?', 'answer': 'A: Unfortunately, no. You only rule cards at sites, not the sites themselves.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Grand%20Mask.webp,
Horned Mask,Relic,Power,Action : Swap one of your faceup advisers with a card at your site.,"[{'question': 'Q: Do I gain favor for swapping a card into the site?', 'answer': 'A: No. A ‘swap’ is not a ‘play.’'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Horned%20Mask.webp,
Cup of Plenty,Relic,Trade,Spend no Supply if you're trading with a card that matches any of your advisers.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Cup%20of%20Plenty.webp,
Whistle,Relic,Power,"Action : Choose a pawn at another site. they must travel to your site if able, spending no Supply. If they do, give them the secret here.","[{'question': 'Q: If I’m inThe Hidden Place, can I force them to flip over a secret to travel to me?', 'answer': 'A: No. They have to be willing to flip it over. You do not have power over their resources.'}, {'question': 'Q: If they’re in another region and theNarrow Passis in my region, will Whistle work?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. They won’t be able to travel to you, unless you’re at the Narrow Pass.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I have the  Vow of Silence, do I have to give the secret away?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. Expect that your Whistle is going to get stolen soon!'}, {'question': 'Q: Do they get the secret face up or down?', 'answer': 'A: Face up.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Whistle.webp,
Dowsing Sticks,Relic,Power,Action : Draw a relic. Take it or put it on the bottom of the relic deck.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Dowsing%20Sticks.webp,
Cracked Horn,Relic,Search,You may put all the cards you discard on the bottom of the world deck.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I bury Visions? What does that do to the Visions Drawn track?', 'answer': 'A: Yes you can, and it does not do anything to the Visions Drawn track.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Cracked%20Horn.webp,
Bandit Crown,Relic,,"Act as if bandits are your warbands except at sites ruled by enemies. They cannot be killed, moved, or sacrificed.","[{'question': 'Q: So do I basically get an extra warband at sites I rule if I have this?', 'answer': 'A: Yup! A site you rule with one physical warband basically has two, since you count bandits as warbands.'}, {'question': 'Q: If I have the Bandit Crown, can I take the last warband off my site as a minor action (6.5)? Likewise, can I simply put a warband on a site with no warbands on it?', 'answer': 'A: Yes to both! The bandit there counts as your warband, so you’re not really taking your last one off the site, and you rule empty sites.'}, {'question': 'Q: What does ‘your warbands’ refer to exactly?', 'answer': 'A: As an Exile, they are your color of warbands. As the Chancellor or a Citizen, they are purple warbands. But if you’re a Citizen and attack an Imperial player, they revert to your color of warbands for that campaign.'}, {'question': 'Q: Do purple warbands get added to empty sites if I have the Bandit Crown and become a Citizen or flip up facedown sites while I am a Citizen?', 'answer': 'A: Nope. Keep the sites empty, though they are still ruled by the Empire.'}, {'question': 'Q: In the Chronicle, if I win, do I discard sites with no warbands?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! You rule them.'}, {'question': 'Q: In the Chronicle, if I win as the Chancellor and a Citizen has the Bandit Crown, do I discard sites with no warbands?', 'answer': 'A: No, You rule those sites as well. The Citizen’s warbands are purple, and they treat bandits as their warbands.'}, {'question': 'Q: In the Chronicle, if I win as an Exile and make another Exile with the Bandit Crown into a Citizen, what happens?', 'answer': 'A: You’ll place a warband on all of the sites they rule, even sites they had no warbands on.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Bandit%20Crown.webp,
Ring of Devotion,Relic,,"You cannot place warbands at sites. When mustering, you gain two more warbands.","[{'question': 'Q: What cases does this cover?', 'answer': 'A: All of them! You can campaign against sites but you can’t place warbands at them. You can’t drop off warbands using a minor action (6.5). You can’t useWarning Signalsto move warbands around. And so on.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Ring%20of%20Devotion.webp,
Skeleton Key,Relic,Power,"Action : If the Chancellor rules your site, peek at any one relic in the Imperial Reliquary, and you may take it.","[{'question': 'Q: Can the Chancellor use this?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! The other players should probably think about getting the Skeleton Key away from the Chancellor.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Skeleton%20Key.webp,
Oracular Pig,Relic,,Action : Peek at the top three cards of the world deck.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Oracular%20Pig.webp,
Circlet of Command,Relic,,"Players cannot target or take your banners or your other relics. In campaigns, banishing your pawn and favor adds one more defense die .","[{'question': 'Q: If I have a banner, can I recover it from myself?', 'answer': 'A: Yes you can. More accurately, this card should say ‘Other players...’'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Circlet%20of%20Command.webp,
Ivory Eye,Relic,Power,"Action : Peek at any facedown site, adviser, or relic at any site.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Ivory%20Eye.webp,
Map,Relic,,Action : Put this relic on the bottom of the relic deck to gain 4 Supply.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Map.webp,
Obsidian Cage,Relic,Battle Plan,"If you're victorious, move all unkilled warbands in your enemy's force to the Obsidian Cage. Action : Move any number of warbands from Obsidian Cage to any board of the same color.","[{'question': 'Q: How does this interact withHospital?', 'answer': 'A: Warbands that would be killed are placed on Hospital’s site, as long as that player still rules it. Then, any warbands in that player’s force are put on Obsidian Cage.'}, {'question': 'Q: What happens to warbands on this card if it is returned to the relic deck?', 'answer': 'A: The player who holds it must return all the warbands as described on its Action power.'}, {'question': 'Q: What happens to Exile warbands if the Exile becomes a Citizen?', 'answer': 'A: They remain the same color while on the Cage. If they are returned, they must return to that Exile and become purple.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Obsidian%20Cage.webp,
Book of Records,Relic,Search,You must gain secret instead of favor when you play to a site.,"[{'question': 'Q: How does this interact with theFertile Valley?', 'answer': 'A: If you play a Hearth card to the Fertile Valley, you will get one secret (for playing to a site) and one favor (for playing to the Fertile Valley specifically).'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Book%20of%20Records.webp,
Dragonskin Drum,Relic,Travel,"After traveling, gain one warband.","[{'question': 'Q: Do I get a warband if someone forces me to travel?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Dragonskin%20Drum.webp,
The Grand Scepter,Relic,,"You cannot use this if you took it on this turn. Action : Peek in the Imperial Reliquary. Action : Offer Citizenship to any Exile, or exile a Citizen except yourself.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I use the Scepter on the same turn that I got it if I was given it in an exchange?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! Take and give are unique keywords, so feel free. Thematically, you were freely given the power to use it, rather than seizing it.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/The%20Grand%20Scepter.webp,
Conspiracy,Vision,," When Played : You may burn secret to take one relic or banner from a player whose pawn is at your site. If it's a banner, it burns favor  favor / secret  secret . To do so, you must have at least two advisers whose suits match any of their adviers. Return this card to the box.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I choose to not burn the secret and just return the card to the box?', 'answer': 'A: Yes! It says ‘You may...’'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Conspiracy.webp,
Vision of Faith,Vision,, Wake : You win if you hold the Darkest Secret and at least three visions have been drawn from the deck.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vision%20of%20Faith.webp,
Vision of Rebellion,Vision,, Wake : You win if you hold the People's Favor and at least three visions have been drawn from the deck.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vision%20of%20Rebellion.webp,
Vision of Sanctuary,Vision,," Wake : You win if you hold the most relics and banners, and at least three visions have been drawn from the deck.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vision%20of%20Sanctuary.webp,
Vision of Conquest,Vision,, Wake : You win if you rule the most sites and at least three visions have been drawn from the deck.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Vision%20of%20Conquest.webp,
Ancient City,Site,Search,"If you play an suit\-order card to this site, and you have not discarded an suit\-order card here during this turn, you get 2 warbands.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Ancient%20City.webp,2.0
Barren Coast,Site,Travel,"When traveling from here to a Coast site, the Travel cost is 1 Supply and you ignore the Narrow Pass tower.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Barren%20Coast.webp,1.0
Buried Giant,Site,Travel,"When traveling from here, you may flip one secret on your board facedown to spend no Supply and ignore the Narrow Pass power.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Buried%20Giant.webp,2.0
Charming Valley,Site,Travel,"When traveling from here, increase the Travel cost by 1 Supply.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Charming%20Valley.webp,3.0
Deep Woods,Site,Search,"If you play a suit\-beast card to this site, and you have not discarded a suit\-beast card here during this turn, you take the relic here, treating this as recovering it.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Deep%20Woods.webp,2.0
Drowned City,Site,,"At the end of your Wake Phase, if your pawn is here, you may take one secret from this site.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Drowned%20City.webp,
Fertile Valley,Site,Search,"If you play a heart card to this site, and you have not discarded a suit\-hearth card here during this turn, you get favor .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Fertile%20Valley.webp,3.0
Great Slum,Site,Search,"When playing or moving a card to this site, you may discard a card here first.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Great%20Slum.webp,3.0
The Tribunal,Site,,"Action : If you rule this site or your pawn is here, negotiate a binding exchange of favor and secret as well as binding actions at any future time, in any combination, with any player.","[{'question': 'Q: What does ‘any time’ mean? The same game? Future games?', 'answer': 'A: Whatever your group agrees to. This falls under the Group Agreements guidance in the playbook involving metagame play.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/The%20Tribunal.webp,2.0
Lush Coast,Site,Travel,"When traveling from here to a Coast site, the Travel cost is 1 Supply and you ignore the Narrow Pass tower.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Lush%20Coast.webp,3.0
Marshes,Site,Search,"When searching, you must draw one fewer card if your pawn is here.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Marshes.webp,2.0
Mine,Site,,"At the end of your Wake Phase, if your pawn is here, you may take one favor from this site.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Mine.webp,1.0
Mountain,Site,Campaign,You must subtract one dicer if you declare any number of targets at this site .,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Mountain.webp,2.0
Narrow Pass,Site,Campaign,"When traveling from another region to this region, you must Travel to this site. When campaigning, if you declare any targets in this region and your pawn is in a different region, you must target this site unless you rule it.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Narrow%20Pass.webp,1.0
Plains,Site,Campaign,You must add one dicer if you declare any number of targets at this site .,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Plains.webp,3.0
River,Site,Muster,"When mustering from a card at this site, you gain one more warband if you rule this site.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/River.webp,2.0
Rocky Coast,Site,Travel,"When traveling from here to a Coast site, the Travel cost is 1 Supply and you ignore the Narrow Pass tower.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Rocky%20Coast.webp,2.0
Salt Flats,Site,,"At the end of your Wake Phase, if your pawn is here, you may take one favor or secret from this site.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Salt%20Flats.webp,2.0
Shrouded Wood,Site,Travel,"When traveling from here, the Travel cost is 2 Supply, and you ignore the Narrow Pass and The Hidden Place powers. If an enemy rules here, you travel to the site of the ruler's choice , even if another player is making you travel.","[{'question': 'Q: If someone forces me to travel away from here and I rule this site, do I get to choose where to go?', 'answer': 'A: No. The power of the Shrouded Wood applies when an enemy rules it, not when you rule it.'}, {'question': 'Q: If someone forces me to travel away from here and a different enemy rules this site, do they get to choose where I go?', 'answer': 'A: Yes!'}, {'question': 'Q: If the Chancellor is Decadent and travels from this site to a Hinterland site, how many Supply does this cost?', 'answer': 'A: Three. The base Travel cost is two, and Decadent adds one more.'}, {'question': 'Q: What happens if I want to travel from here, but the bandits rule this site?', 'answer': 'A: Travel as normal. This site text needs a small errata, changing ‘enemy’ to ‘enemy player.’'}, {'question': 'Q: How does this work if the Clockwork Prince rules it?', 'answer': 'A: Under Limited Powers, travel as normal. Under Expanded Powers, your desination is chosen by the player with discretion, as described in Expanded Powers.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Shrouded%20Wood.webp,2.0
Standing Stones,Site,Search,"If you play an suit\-arcane card to this site, and you have not discarded an suit\-arcane card here during this turn, you get secret .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Standing%20Stones.webp,2.0
Steppe,Site,Search,"If you play a suit\-nomad card to this site, and you have not discarded a suit\-nomad card here during this turn, you get secret .",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Steppe.webp,2.0
The Hidden Place,Site,Campaign,You cannot travel to here or declare campaign targets here unless you flip one secret on your board facedown.,"[{'question': 'Q: Can I be forced to travel here?', 'answer': 'A: Only if you choose to flip a secret.'}, {'question': 'Q: If a travel to the site, do I still have to flip another secret if I declare campaign targets at the site?', 'answer': 'A: Yup! So if you traveled to the site and then targeted the site and a pawn there, you would need to flip two secrets.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/The%20Hidden%20Place.webp,2.0
Wastes,Site,Search,"If you play a suit\-discord card to this site, and you have not discarded a suit\-discord card here during this turn, you get take the relic here, treating this as recovering it.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Wastes.webp,1.0
Banner of the Darkest Secret,Search,Recover,"Recovery : Players can only recover this from you if there is a card at your site whose suit does not match any of your advisers. The new holder must place more secret than old secret here, then takes one secret from the old secret here, and the old holder takes the rest. Search : Spend 2 Supply if you're drawing from the world deck .","[{'question': 'Q: Can I recover this from someone if they have no cards at their site?', 'answer': 'A: Nope.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I recover this from someone who has no advisers if they have cards at their site?', 'answer': 'A: Yes you can! This is an errata.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does anything happen to the secrets on this if I give away the banner?', 'answer': 'A: Nope!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Banner%20of%20the%20Darkest%20Secret.webp,
Banner of the Mob's Favor,Search,Recover,"Recovery : Put more favor here than old favor . Put old favor in the favor banks, one by one, starting with any suit. Then, flip this banner. Wake : You must put favor here or move favor here to the favor bank with the least favor . Do this twice. Search : When playing to site, you may first discard a denizen card at any site in your region, and you may play to any site in your region.","[{'question': 'Q: Can I place one favor and return one favor, or do I have to do the same thing twice?', 'answer': 'A: You may place one favor and return one favor, keeping its value the same.'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Banner%20of%20the%20Mob's%20Favor.webp,
Banner of the People's Favor,Search,Recover,"Recovery : Put more favor here than old favor . Put old favor in the favor banks, one by one, starting with any suit. Wake : You must put favor here or move favor here to the favor bank with the least favor . Then, if this banner has 6+ favor , flip it. Search : When playing to site, you may first discard a denizen card at any site in your region, and you may play to any site in your region.","[{'question': 'Q: What happens if I have no favor to put on it during my Wake Phase, but it only has one favor on it?', 'answer': 'A: Nothing. It stays at one favor.'}, {'question': 'Q: Can I use this to play cards to facedown sites?', 'answer': 'A: Nope! They have no capacity for cards.'}, {'question': 'Q: Does anything happen to the favor on this if I give away the banner?', 'answer': 'A: Nope!'}]",https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Banner%20of%20the%20People's%20Favor.webp,
Oathkeeper of Devotion,Victory condition,,Oathkeeper of Devotion holds the Darkest Secret. Successor to the Chancellor holds the Grand Scepter.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Oathkeeper%20of%20Devotion.webp,
Oathkeeper of Protection,Victory condition,,Oathkeeper of Protection holds the most relics and banners. Successor to the Chancellor holds the People's Favor.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Oathkeeper%20of%20Protection.webp,
Oathkeeper of Supremacy,Victory condition,,Oathkeeper of Supremacy rules the most sites. Successor to the Chancellor holds more relics and banners.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Oathkeeper%20of%20Supremacy.webp,
Oathkeeper of the People,Victory condition,,Oathkeeper of the People holds the People's Favor. Successor to the Chancellor holds the Darkest Secret.,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Oathkeeper%20of%20the%20People.webp,
Brutal,Campaign,,"If you're the attacker, the defeated player  must kill all warbands in their force.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Brutal.webp,
Careless,Trade,,You gain one more favor  . You must gain one less secret when trading for secret .,[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Careless.webp,
Decadent,Travel,,"Spend no Supply if you're traveling to a site in the Cradle from a site in the Provinces or Hinterland. If you're traveling to a site in the Hinterland, increase the Travel cost by 1 Supply.",[],https://ledercardcdn.seiyria.com/cards/oath/en-US/Decadent.webp,
